A diagonal run.
Diagonal run.
Wow.
What do you mean?
What is that?
That's the move's name.
And it's running in at a diagonal.
These days, soccer teams use what's referred to as zone defense,
meaning each player is assigned to a specific area,
and so if any opponent happens to invade that space,
they're instantly tackled.
But if someone decides to run through those areas at a diagonal angle,
it confuses the defenders.
They don't know who's supposed to make the tackle
and how long they should stay on them,
or if it's worth breaking the formation.
It becomes a whole bunch of problems to solve all at once.
Still, because the diagonal run tends to be a surprise attack,
it doesn't seem to work well most of the time.
But somehow he did it.
Aoi's timing on this bold move was rare perfection.
The moment he chose to run across the defenders
was the worst moment for them.
But how could he know that?
I bet it's because...
Now that he's been playing defense,
he understands how defenders think.
The diagonal run, it works.
It really works.
I've got so many ideas about different ways to score,
flooding my brain right now.
We're about to make our comeback,
and it's gonna be awesome.
Good?
Good game.
Boom.
Oh, boom.
Mark 33! Do not let him pass! We can't let that fullback have free reign!
Why are we marking a wimp like Aoi?
Come on, Kurada! Just give me the frickin' ball this time!
Why when you're being marked? Do you have something in mind?
What the heck? He hit it right back to me?
There's not any spin on it, so it's easy to keep it at my feet.
Is he wanting me to just hold it here?
Think, Kurada, think! Since the ball is at your feet, you're free to check out where all the spaces are!
You got this! You can set up a move wherever you send the ball!
Oh, I get it now! Back during the Inner Squad match in April.
The type of pass should have clued you in right away.
I wondered what the heck he was talking about. Makes sense now.
On top of making eye contact and barking instructions, I can also send different messages with the types of passes I make.
I thought I knew everything. Then something clicked. There's so much more to soccer than I realized.
What the... He's pushed all the way up here? Does he not know he's a fullback?
No. No. No. He's been very useful today.
His positioning may be bizarre, but I can tell he's got a plan.
Sugawara! Coming back to you!
Just keep it there!
I'm moving them. It's all rearranged. Because of me, everything changed.
Awesome.
There's a perfect way to score. And you're the only one capable of it.
Owie!
Point the toes of my planted foot where I want it to go.
Then hit the middle of the ball with the top of my foot.
They switched to play?
It's like the field...
just became part of me!
What? Another diagonal?
That's the second time. An unplanned diagonal run by a fullback.
That tricky goal they conceded is still fresh in their minds.
No way they come out strong.
Why is no one putting pressure on him?
Yeah! I've got him!
Here!
I hear you!
I'm more of a cautious, sensible type of player.
So high-risk diagonal runs aren't really my thing.
I never do them.
But when you switched the play earlier, the moment you kicked the ball,
you looked right at me and I knew.
That smile just screamed,
let's go kick their asses!
Right?
Huh? Another diagonal run?
Whoa! That was sweet, Ajito!
Now we're open!
Even when he's at that range,
Owie would normally try to force a shot.
He's almost to the vine line!
What was it?
You called it a diagonal run?
I think... maybe?
That right?
Running from the middle to right there?
Watch the flank! Look out!
Confusion.
The secret sauce.
If I can confuse the crap out of him like this,
it doesn't matter who finishes it.
And since it doesn't,
it could be me.
I actually scored.
My boy, Ajito!
It's been a while.
That felt amazing!
Give him one more hit!
What kind of monster is he?
He orchestrated all of that on his own.
And he's still only a first year?
The momentum's with us now.
One goal!
Just one goal behind!
We've got this!
Don't know about that.
If you're trying to mark me out of the game,
it's probably not gonna work.
Mikami!
If we have two people marking 33,
that leaves space open in the middle!
I can't believe you did it again, are we?
It's just like last year.
Almost all of the candidates had lost the will to keep fighting.
Then there was you.
You never gave up.
You just kept on running.
You forged a new path.
The way you did today,
and right behind you,
were those same two from before.
There are those who move forward,
and those who refuse.
There are those who go pro,
and those who go home.
Nothing's changed since then.
Not a damn thing.
Including me.
Does that mean
I'm just a fraud after all?
I could never play the game like him.
Kaneda!
Drop back!
You're on defense!
Kaneda!
Don't move!
Stay right there!
We still need you at the front!
Hey, coach!
Kaneda doesn't need to drop back!
He should stay up top!
Give it to Kaneda!
We're sticking to our usual style of play.
Is that clear to everyone?
Yeah!
The thing about Musashino FC Youth
is that we're a collection of players
who didn't make it into the J Youth teams.
We all still dream of going pro.
We know we have our own strength.
And yet,
we have the same setbacks.
Esperion.
They're a team of monsters.
They shove their advantages
in our faces again and again.
They're what we want to be,
so they're our greatest fear.
Kaneda joined us last year
in the summer.
I remember.
It was just after I was made the new captain.
I'm using this team
as a springboard for going pro.
I want to score as many goals as I can.
So just keep sending the damn ball my way.
Especially against Esperion.
Who the hell do you think you are?
Coming in here,
telling us what to do?
I couldn't understand
why manager Satake recruited this guy.
Not at first, anyway.
But...
He kept boldly claiming
he'd be going pro one day.
That he would beat Esperion.
And he scored enough goals
to back it up.
Huh?
That's the second time
it's happened out there!
You've caused us so much trouble
for an entire year.
You're watching this damn game?
It's not fair, man!
At the same time,
I can't deny I've learned
a whole lot from you.
And Star Players lead the line.
So, okay.
We'll all pass the ball to you.
Our team is not going to lose
to Esperion.
Make sure of it.
Of course we aren't.
This game's not over.
It's just starting!
I'll score!
Send me the damn ball!
I see you, Kanada.
It's been a year since that day.
A lot's changed.
And we both get to play
on amazing teams.
Achito!
Kur hole!
Nuh!
Ugh.
Huh?
No!
Ugh!
Thank you!
we won man those guys are a piece of work they threw everything they had at us right up to the
final whistle i've never expended so much energy in a game before yeah but it was really the best
game we ever played i hope all our games are that exciting aren't you hardcore well that's
encouraging togashi kuroda otomo ajito tomorrow you're on the a-team
did that just happen wait i'm on the a-team
yeah you're doing it just don't let it fall
coach nozomi
what's all that noise from upstairs oh that's um
we're all celebrating our win and promotions of course we're in otomo's room
you're all easily pleased you may have beaten mushishino one of the top rated teams but
we're still low on the list
what are you bowing for
i didn't expect this getting promoted to the a-team
i know it's because of you it doesn't mean you're safe if you can't maintain your skills on the a-team
you'll be right back on b-team in no time
i understand i'm still grateful to you
that was quite a thorough beating well done what a wonderful tactical exchange they had
i'm impressed you're an excellent commander
thank you but i'm just the head coach today's win was still a narrow escape for us
yeah maybe so but if that number 33 wasn't playing then we might have had a chance
what amazes me the most is the fact that asperian was even able to find someone like him in the first place
there's nothing really special about him that stands out in terms of his skills or physical conditioning
normally he'd get overlooked in favor of other players with more skill
but you really made a great call there
you got a glimpse of ashito aoi's talent and snatched him up
that's the true potential of jay youth
you truly are improving at an incredible rate
but the a-team is no cakewalk
i don't want you to take it for granted
when players get their promotion they almost always struggle at first and come right back
even when it feels too tough i want you to hang on for dear life and just keep going
keep believing in the potential you have
build yourself back up one step at a time
you've got what it takes to survive
you have my word
you're not gonna join the celebration
i figured you'd be a lot happier
considering your good news
it just hasn't sunk in
did i use up all my excitement during the game?
it's like my brain knows what happened but my heart still doesn't
awww
this sucks
woah hana
what are you doing out here ashito can't you see it's raining?
it's raining? hurry and get back to the dorm
hana it happened i did it
for real i'm on the a-team
i got promoted i did it
hana can you believe it?
hana?
i'm just kidding
did you believe me?
uh
good for you my man
a-team huh?
no one deserves a more brah
anyway better get home before we drown
what? what the heck just happened?
um you don't need to hang out here with me
the dorm's not far
actually i'm gonna run
don't jump out from there
and that's why i told you not to jump off
hm
it's the b-team field
has the worst drainage ever
so when it rains
you might as well bust out your rowboat and swimming suit
oh man training sessions in the rain were so difficult to get through
but i'm not gonna have to deal with that anymore on the a-team field
hey
are you seriously doing this?
it's just a spring rain i can make it
would you just cut it out?
come on why are you acting so weird?
because i'm weird
i can't talk to you now
i-i have to go
uh
uh?
i know i'm acting weird
i feel weird
so uh
it's old man Fukuda you were talking about huh?
you know
when you told me about that player you really love
am i right?
mystery solved
when i was little i thought i was gonna marry him
hmm
and you're not even all that into soccer
that old man must have been one heck of a player
wow
he really was
and i got to watch him play with my own two eyes
whenever his team was playing
that stadium was no soccer arena
it was more like an amphitheater
with a concert about to start
it was so exciting
on those days
my brother was the star
and everyone there knew it
it was unforgettable
if he hadn't gotten injured
if he hadn't
okay
i think i have you figured out
so since the old man can't play anymore
you decided you'd root for me
huh?
you told me about your favorite player
and then you told me i reminded you of him
i remember
that means
you think he and i
you look nothing alike
aww
guess i'll have to settle for being sexy
but i
kinda wish you'd cheer for me for being me
huh?
your cheering has powers
gives me strength
i mean
haven't you noticed that every time you come to watch me play i win?
like a good luck charm
it's crazy
uh
is that true?
does my cheering really
help you in some way?
what? i'm not just making it up
hearing you cheer is everything
you help me even more than you know
and now there you go acting all weird again
as of tomorrow i'm on the A team
quit making your face like that
at least send me off with a bang
i need you to cheer
that's what fans are supposed to do
huh?